<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:base="http://ehqo.net/">
  <title>Ehqo’s Echoes</title>
  <subtitle>A blog written by Ehqo.</subtitle>
  <link href="http://ehqo.net/feed.xml" rel="self" />
  <link href="http://ehqo.net/" />
  
  <updated>2024-03-09T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <id>http://ehqo.net/</id>
  <author>
    <name>Ehqo</name>
    <email>ehqo@omg.lol</email>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>LLMs as Tutors</title>
    <link href="http://ehqo.net/blog/llms-as-tutors/" />
    <updated>2024-03-09T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>http://ehqo.net/blog/llms-as-tutors/</id>
    <content
      xml:lang=""
      type="html"
      >&lt;h3 id=&quot;this-is-not-a-grift-i-promise-lol&quot;&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;heading-anchor&quot; href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/llms-as-tutors/#this-is-not-a-grift-i-promise-lol&quot;&gt;This is not a grift, I promise lol&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently I’ve been reading about how LLMs can be used as a learning partner or tutor to explore topics of interest. I decided to explore this possibility for my own purposes; an exercise I thought would also help me further compare tools like Claude 3, GPT4, and Gemini Advanced to see which would be the best for my needs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Editors Note: I know, I know, who isn’t talking about pRoMptInG and AI these days. There’s so much absolute garbage content out there around AI and LLMs, 99% of which is someone trying to make a quick buck off of a subscription and/or by selling your private data/information. I personally almost feel gross writing about it now, despite the fact that I have nothing to do with any of it. That being said, what follows contains no grifts. I think there are many amazing applications for LLMs that a quiet minority are discussing - and those are the things I want to talk about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My exploration led me to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.moreusefulthings.com/&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;More Useful Things&lt;/a&gt;, the companion site for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.oneusefulthing.org/&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;One Useful Thing&lt;/a&gt;,  a research blog by Dr. Ethan Mollick and Dr. Lilach Mollick of the Wharton School. One Useful Thing explores the implications of AI for work, education, and life in terms that we can all understand. In my opinion, it is a thoughtful, interesting publication that discusses meaningful impacts AI can have on our lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More Useful Things has a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.moreusefulthings.com/prompts&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;prompt library&lt;/a&gt; primarily geared towards use in a classroom/learning setting, all of which follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.oneusefulthing.org/p/working-with-ai-two-paths-to-prompting&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;a structured format&lt;/a&gt;. Most of the prompts are also tailored for a specific LLM of your choosing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The instructor-oriented aids can help generate project ideas, quizzes, syllabi, and even structured prompts themselves. I took a particular interest in this last possibility, since it could be used to create my own customized tutor, based on what level of knowledge I have and what learning goals I want to achieve. In this scenario, I am both teacher (in creating the prompt) and student (in using the prompt I created to access a customized tutor.) What I found was that the LLMs asked me questions to generate a structured prompt capable of asking open-ended leading questions. I believe this to be an &lt;em&gt;extremely strong&lt;/em&gt; tool for anyone looking to study or learn more about literally anything in a customized manner. &lt;sup class=&quot;footnote-ref&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/llms-as-tutors/#fn1&quot; id=&quot;fnref1&quot;&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The prompt library’s section oriented for student-use also includes a “General Tutor” prompt, but I believe the extra step described in the last paragraph allows for a more tailored experience. Other student-oriented prompts include a negotiation simulator, a mentor, class reflection aid, and even a scenario where the LLM plays devil’s advocate. I have yet to try all of these out, but I fully intend to revisit them when need arises.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Dr.’s Mollick have created something incredibly special here. It’s often been said that the internet changed the way we learn forever.&lt;sup class=&quot;footnote-ref&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/llms-as-tutors/#fn2&quot; id=&quot;fnref2&quot;&gt;[2]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; The internet gave anyone with a connection access to near infinite knowledge. However, the biggest shortcoming of learning on the current internet is you have to know what to look for and where to find it. Now, using the vast knowledge of LLMs, we can ask questions and be asked questions in an accessible, interactive learning environment from the comfort of wherever we are. On top of this, our tutors can adjust their approach dynamically based on our needs and the ways we learn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think we are extremely close to this technology being truly accessible to everyone, and I cannot wait to see how it unfolds.&lt;sup class=&quot;footnote-ref&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/llms-as-tutors/#fn3&quot; id=&quot;fnref3&quot;&gt;[3]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Until then, I recommend checking out One Useful Thing and More Useful Things, and trying the prompts to learn more about whatever your heart desires.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr class=&quot;footnotes-sep&quot; /&gt;
&lt;section class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
&lt;ol class=&quot;footnotes-list&quot;&gt;
&lt;li id=&quot;fn1&quot; class=&quot;footnote-item&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I literally cannot express how important I think this capability is. If we can just reduce the amount of ghosts of misinformation in the machine, so to speak, we can essentially provide everyone with a customized learning aid that adapts to what they need and how they learn. &lt;a href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/llms-as-tutors/#fnref1&quot; class=&quot;footnote-backref&quot;&gt;↩︎&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&quot;fn2&quot; class=&quot;footnote-item&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don’t actually know if I made that up, or just think that. But perhaps I’ll expound on why I think that in a later post. &lt;a href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/llms-as-tutors/#fnref2&quot; class=&quot;footnote-backref&quot;&gt;↩︎&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&quot;fn3&quot; class=&quot;footnote-item&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sources. Outside of the need of general availability, I believe a lack of information sources is the biggest shortcoming of current LLM-based learning. It’s important that we not only be able to follow the rabbit trail of information, but also be able to verify that what we are being told is based in fact. &lt;a href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/llms-as-tutors/#fnref3&quot; class=&quot;footnote-backref&quot;&gt;↩︎&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
</content
    >
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>My New Home Online</title>
    <link href="http://ehqo.net/blog/my-new-home-online/" />
    <updated>2024-03-04T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>http://ehqo.net/blog/my-new-home-online/</id>
    <content
      xml:lang=""
      type="html"
      >&lt;p&gt;Well, I think I’m finally home. If you’ve been following along on &lt;a href=&quot;https://social.lol/@ehqo&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Mastodon&lt;/a&gt;, Discord, or the other places I talk online, you’ve seen me try out a swath of blogging platforms and hosts like &lt;a href=&quot;https://weblog.lol/&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Weblog&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://bearblog.dev/&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Bearblog&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://scribbles.page/&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Scribbles&lt;/a&gt;.  In my usual fashion, I’ve spent alot of time thinking about how to best do something, rather than actually doing the thing. The ‘thing’ in this case is writing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanted a place that I could call my own to share my thoughts, as well as other stuff I collect and find interesting, like links and resources. I really thought Bearblog was going to solve this need, but &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fear_of_missing_out&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;FOMO&lt;/a&gt; got the best of me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://rknight.me/&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Alot&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://weblog.anniegreens.lol/&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;of&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://flamedfury.com/&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;really&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://gkeenan.co/&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;cool&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://coryd.dev/&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;people&lt;/a&gt; all maintain their own websites in one way or another and damnit, I want to join them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you couldn’t already tell, I like simplicity.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.11ty.dev/&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Eleventy&lt;/a&gt;, the static site generator, was exactly what I was looking for - simple, easy to work with, and infinitely extendable. And so I took the design work I had done for my Bearblog and implemented it here using &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lenesaile.com/en/&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Lene Saile’s&lt;/a&gt; Eleventy Excellent starter. Lene has done an excellent job in giving folks a head start on building their own site with Eleventy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This leads us to &lt;a href=&quot;https://ehqo.net/&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;ehqo.net&lt;/a&gt;, my final resting place. And no, not in the morbid way. I’m determined to build this site into something I’m proud to call my own.  If you poke around, I’m sure you’ll find some empty spaces, quirks, and bugs. I plan on treating it as my digital garden - a place that will grow and change over time, as I do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had every intention of ending this post with a smart, introspective thought about doing things with intention and purpose. But alas, my brain and eyes are tired from staring at code all evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So for now - remember to drink some water, give someone a compliment, and stay awesome.&lt;/p&gt;
</content
    >
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>My 2024 App Defaults</title>
    <link href="http://ehqo.net/blog/my-2024-app-defaults/" />
    <updated>2024-03-04T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>http://ehqo.net/blog/my-2024-app-defaults/</id>
    <content
      xml:lang=""
      type="html"
      >&lt;p&gt;Shortly after creating my omg.lol account at the tail end of 2023, I came across Robb Knight’s post - &lt;a href=&quot;https://defaults.rknight.me/&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Hemispheric Views - App Defaults&lt;/a&gt;. Inspired by the countless folks who contributed, I figured I would throw my hat in the ring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be reviewing and revising this list over 2024. What will I be using next year? Will my needs and goals even be the same? I’m excited about the idea of personal change-logs, and this seems like a great place to start. I intend on creating similar entries to document how my life changes throughout the year. Even since originally writing this post, I have tried to simplify my personal tech-stack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;my-list&quot;&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;heading-anchor&quot; href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/my-2024-app-defaults/#my-list&quot;&gt;My List&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;list&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📨 Mail Client - Spark Mail Classic, Proton&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📮 Mail Server - Gmail, Proton&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📝 Notes - Drafts + Bear&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;✅ To-Do - Todoist&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🟦 Photo Management - Photos.app&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📆 Calendar - Fantastical&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📁 Cloud File Storage - iCloud, Google Drive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📖 Feeds &amp;amp; Read-it-later - NetNewsWire, Omnivore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🙍🏻‍♂️ Contacts - Contacts.app&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🌐 Browser - Firefox&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;💬 Chat - Discord&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🔖 Bookmarks - Anybox&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📜 Word Processing - Docs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📈 Spreadsheets - Excel/Sheets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📊 Presentations - Slides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;💰 Budgeting / Finance - YNAB&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🎧 Music - Spotify/Soundcloud&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🎤 Podcasts - Overcast&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🐘 Mastodon Client - Ice Cubes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🖥 Terminal - Tabby&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🧰 Code Editor - Visual Studio Code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🚀 Launcher - Raycast&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;⠀Changelog:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;list&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2024-02-21 - Added NetNewsWire&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2024-02-11 - Moved from weblog to bearblog. Added Bear, removed Obsidian (remains as a backup), removed Readwise Reader, added Omnivore, removed Reminders, added Todoist, removed Spotify (podcasts), added Overcast, added Proton.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;list&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2024-01-25 - Removed Bear, removed Todoist, removed Reeder, removed Matrix, removed Raindrop, removed Copilot, Removed Ivory. Added Drafts, added Reminders.app, added Readwise Reader, added Anybox, added YNAB, added Icecubes. Changed “RSS” to “Feeds &amp;amp; Read-it-later”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2023-12-29 - Added dev tools and changed some copy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content
    >
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>My Coffee Defaults</title>
    <link href="http://ehqo.net/blog/my-coffee-defaults/" />
    <updated>2024-01-04T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>http://ehqo.net/blog/my-coffee-defaults/</id>
    <content
      xml:lang=""
      type="html"
      >&lt;h1 id=&quot;my-coffee-defaults&quot;&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;heading-anchor&quot; href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/my-coffee-defaults/#my-coffee-defaults&quot;&gt;My Coffee Defaults&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inspired by a few folks in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://32bit.cafe/&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;32bit.cafe&lt;/a&gt; Discord, I figured I’d make a riff on the App Defaults project by &lt;a href=&quot;https://knight.me/&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Robb Knight&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://listen.hemisphericviews.com/097&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Hemispheric Views&lt;/a&gt; - this time with &lt;strong&gt;coffee.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve been told by my better-three-quarters that I am not allowed to bring any more coffee contraptions into the home. This is probably for the best, because I have previously done alot of experiments with brewing. I will say though, I don’t consider myself a “bean connoisseur” by any remote sense of the term. While I have my preferred tastes and methods, there’s nothing quite like a cup of joe slung by an aloof waitress at a tri-state diner. Below, I’ll share my current go-to tools and beans. If you have any questions, or would like to share your own “Coffee Defaults”, reach out via &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:ehqo@omg.lol&quot;&gt;email&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://social.lol/@ehqo&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Mastodon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;primary-brewer&quot;&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;heading-anchor&quot; href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/my-coffee-defaults/#primary-brewer&quot;&gt;Primary Brewer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://noctua.b-cdn.net/images/blog/JAN24/espro-p7.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;p7-french-press-by-espro&quot;&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;heading-anchor&quot; href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/my-coffee-defaults/#p7-french-press-by-espro&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://espro.com/collections/french-press/products/coffee-french-press-p7&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;P7 French Press by Espro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;why-i-like-it&quot;&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;heading-anchor&quot; href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/my-coffee-defaults/#why-i-like-it&quot;&gt;Why I like it:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;list&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Durable, stainless steel design, keeps things nice and toasty&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Double micro-filter for a smoother, grit-free cup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;beans&quot;&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;heading-anchor&quot; href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/my-coffee-defaults/#beans&quot;&gt;Beans&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;seasonal-festive-lights-by-rook-coffee&quot;&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;heading-anchor&quot; href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/my-coffee-defaults/#seasonal-festive-lights-by-rook-coffee&quot;&gt;Seasonal: &lt;a href=&quot;https://rookcoffee.com/collections/coffee&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Festive Lights by Rook Coffee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://noctua.b-cdn.net/images/blog/JAN24/festive-lights.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;why-i-like-it-1&quot;&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;heading-anchor&quot; href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/my-coffee-defaults/#why-i-like-it-1&quot;&gt;Why I like it:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;list&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you’ve ever visited New Jersey, you might have heard of Rook Coffee. This place is wildly good, and I wish they would expand their footprint out of state. Their seasonal holiday blend maintains their high standard of quality with a delicious cup that makes me which I purchased more before it sold out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please for the love of the coffee gods, try &lt;a href=&quot;https://rookcoffee.com/collections/cold-brew&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Rook’s cold brew concentrate&lt;/a&gt;. I’d recommend the New Orleans Style. It’s worth every penny and you will be upset at me for recommending it, because you’ll be throwing your wallet at their website fiending for more once you try it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;standardtrader-joes-wake-up-blend&quot;&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;heading-anchor&quot; href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/my-coffee-defaults/#standardtrader-joes-wake-up-blend&quot;&gt;Standard:&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.traderjoes.com/home/products/pdp/organic-fair-trade-wake-up-blend-coffee-098530&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Trader Joe’s Wake Up Blend&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://noctua.b-cdn.net/images/blog/JAN24/tj-wakeup-blend.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;why-i-like-it-2&quot;&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;heading-anchor&quot; href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/my-coffee-defaults/#why-i-like-it-2&quot;&gt;Why I like it:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;list&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Look, I said I’m not a bean connoisseur. This stuff just tastes good and is dependable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sweet notes, with a little bit of acidity. A good way to start any day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;coffee-storage&quot;&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;heading-anchor&quot; href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/my-coffee-defaults/#coffee-storage&quot;&gt;Coffee Storage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;airscape-kilo-coffee-canister-by-planetary-design&quot;&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;heading-anchor&quot; href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/my-coffee-defaults/#airscape-kilo-coffee-canister-by-planetary-design&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://planetarydesign.com/product/airscape-kilo-coffee-canister/&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Airscape Kilo Coffee Canister by Planetary Design&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://noctua.b-cdn.net/images/blog/JAN24/airscape-kilo.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;why-i-like-it-3&quot;&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;heading-anchor&quot; href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/my-coffee-defaults/#why-i-like-it-3&quot;&gt;Why I like it:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;list&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This sucker holds &lt;em&gt;alot&lt;/em&gt; of coffee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The over-engineered design of the air-tight seal geek-worthy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;kettle&quot;&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;heading-anchor&quot; href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/my-coffee-defaults/#kettle&quot;&gt;Kettle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;clyde-stovetop-kettle-by-fellow&quot;&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;heading-anchor&quot; href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/my-coffee-defaults/#clyde-stovetop-kettle-by-fellow&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://fellowproducts.com/products/clyde-stovetop-kettle&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Clyde Stovetop Kettle by Fellow&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://noctua.b-cdn.net/images/blog/JAN24/clyde-kettle.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;why-i-like-it-4&quot;&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;heading-anchor&quot; href=&quot;http://ehqo.net/blog/my-coffee-defaults/#why-i-like-it-4&quot;&gt;Why I like it:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;list&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It’s simple, easy to use and clean, and just looks nice, yank?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The two-tone whistle sounds like a train 🚂&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have any thoughts or want to share your own “Coffee Defaults”? Reach out via &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:ehqo@omg.lol&quot;&gt;email&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://social.lol/@ehqo&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Mastodon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content
    >
  </entry>
</feed>
